-What you guys doing? -Monica's making us watch Old Yeller.
你们在干嘛？ 摩妮卡逼我们看“老黄狗”
Why are you guys upset? It's Old Yeller. It's a happy movie.
那你们在伤心什么？ 这是一部快乐的电影啊
-What? -What are you talking about?
什么？ 你在胡扯什么？
Come on. Happy family gets a dog.
少来了，快乐家庭养了一只狗
Frontier fun!
荒野之乐
Pheebs,what about the end?
对呀，但是结局呢？
When Yeller saves the family and everyone's happy?
是老黄救全家人于狼口之中 大家皆大欢喜
That's not the end.
那不是结局
That's when my mother would shut off the TV and say,"The end."
才是呢，我妈会在那个时候 关掉电视说已结束了
What about when he has rabies?
那它生狂犬病的情节呢？
He doesn't have rabies. He has babies.
它没有生狂犬病 它生了小宝宝
That's what my mom said.
我妈说的
I don't think she'd want you to see what's about to happen.
菲比，我猜你妈 不想你看接下来的剧情
Why? What's about to happen?
为什么？接下来怎么样？
I've never seen this part.
这部份我从没看过
Hey,Travis,what you doing with that gun?
崔维，你拿枪干什么？
Oh,no.
不…
No,no,Travis,put down the gun.
崔维，把枪放下来
No,no,he's your buddy. He's your Yeller.
不要…它是你的伙伴 是你的老黄
No! The end! The end!
不…剧终…
Okay,what kind of a sick doggy snuff film is this?
这算什么病态的狗电影？
The One Where Old Yeller Dies
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
六人行 第2季 第20集 猎狗之死
Have you guys eaten? Richard and l just finished,and we've got leftovers.
你们吃过了吗？我跟理查 刚吃过，我们还有剩菜
Chicken and potatoes.
鸡肉跟马铃薯
What am I wearing?
我穿什么？
Actually,nothing but rubber gloves.
事实上，塑胶手套而已
One of these times,you'll really be naked and we won't come over.
有一天你会真的一丝不挂 而我们却不会过来了
I got a leg,three breasts and a wing.
我有条腿，三块胸跟一根翅膀
How do you find clothes that fit?
那你怎么找得到衣服穿？
Hey,Monica? We got a question.
摩妮卡，我们有问题
All right,yes,I see other women in the shower at the gym.
好吧，再说一遍，对，我在 健身房浴室会看到别的女人
And no,I don't look.
不，我目不斜视
No,not that one.
不，不是那个
We're figuring out who to bring to the Nicks game.
我们在想今晚带谁去看 尼克队赛球，我们多了一张票
Ross can't go,so it's between my friend Eric Prower,who has breath issues...
对，罗斯不能去，所以要嘛 就是我朋友包艾力，他有口臭
...and Dan,with the poking. "Did you see that play?"
…或是丹，他爱戳人 “你看到了吗？”
"You want more beer? Is that Spike Lee?"
“还要啤酒吗？” “那是史派克李吗？”
Why don't you ask Richard?
为什么不问理查？
Richard,if you had an extra ticket to the Nicks game...
理查，如果你有多一张 尼克队球赛的票…
...and you had to choose between a friend who smelled...
…而你必须从有口臭…
...and one who bruises you, who would you pick?
…跟会戳人的朋友当中选 你会选谁？
Being a huge Nicks fan myself...
对一个大尼克迷来说…
... I think you should take someone who's a huge Nicks fan.
…我想你们应该选一个 大尼克迷
That's Eric.
那就艾力好了
Glad to be of help. Matches.
乐意效劳，不客气
I meant,why don't you take Richard to the game?
我是说 你们为什么不请理查去？
What?
怎么样？
-I don't know. -Come on!
我不知道 少来了
He keeps his fingers to himself, and he's always minty fresh.
他从来不会乱指乱戳 口气永远芳香自然
Richard's really nice. We just don't know him really well.
理查他这个人真的很好啦 只是我们跟他不是很熟
Plus,he's old
加上他又老…
er than some people.
…对某些人来说
But younger than some buildings.
但他比某些建筑要年轻一点
So what,he's a little older. Big deal.
他老一点又怎么样？
He's important to me.
他对我而言是很重要的
If you ask him, he might take you in his Jag.
你们问他的话 他或许会开积架车去哦
How do we say yes...
我们要怎么说…
...and make it seem like it's not just to ride in the cool car?
…才不会听起来像 为了要搭他的酷车才邀请他去
Okay,this could be tough.
这有点棘手
We'll bring him, but only if he takes the Jaguar.
他如果开积架车来 我们才会带他去
You almost had it.
你差点办到了
No,no,you're fine. You're fine.
不…你没问题…
Hi,honey.
亲爱的
You are not gonna believe what happened!
你们一定不会相信 发生了什么事
We were playing on the floor, and he grabs the table...
我们坐在那边地板上玩 他抓住了桌子…
...and he pulls himself up!
…把自己拉起来了
He pulled himself up!
他把自己拉起来了
Standing man!
他会站
I'm sorry you missed it, but I did tape it if you wanna see it.
很遗撼你们错过，但我 录下来了，你们要看的话…
We know. He already did it last week.
我们知道，他上个礼拜就会了
You can watch our tape if you want.
你可以看我们的带子
See,I don't believe this. I missed the first time of everything.
我真不敢相信 我错过每个第一次了
The first time he rolled over, the first time he crawled.
我错过他第一次翻身 他第一次爬
What else? Has he spoken? Is he driving?
我还错过了什么？ 他说话了吗？会开车了吗？
Does he have a favorite liqueur?
他有偏好的甜酒吗？
He is getting closer on the talking thing.
他好像也快要会说话了
He can't quite say "mama" yet, but once he said "Yemen."
他还不会说妈妈 可是有一次他说“叶门”
See,I don't know. I'm so sick of missing stuff.
我受不了老是错过
I want him for more than a day. I want him for a whole weekend.
我不要只照顾他一天而已 我要他一整个周末
Listen. I feel
你听着，我是说我觉得…
That would be great.
没问题
Really? I had a whole speech prepared.
真的？我正准备要大发议论
Oh,shoot,that would've been fun.
讨厌，那会很好玩的
Did you just see that?
你们看到了吗？
Did you see? He just waved! He just waved!
他刚刚挥手…
He's never waved before!
他从来没有挥过手
Yes,he has. Very good.
他挥过？好极了
What you got there?
菲菲，那是什么？
Love Story,Brian's Song and Terms of Endearment.
“爱的故事”“布莱恩之歌” 还有“亲密关系”
All you need now is The Killing Fields and guacamole,and you got a party!
现在只缺“杀戳战场” 跟一些鹗季酱你就可以狂欢了
I talked to my grandma about the Old Yeller incident...
对呀，我跟我奶奶讲了 那个“老黄狗”那件事…
...and she said my mom used to not show us the ends of sad movies...
…她说我妈总是不让我们看 那种悲伤电影的结局…
...to shield us from the pain and sadness.
…好让我们不用痛苦伤心
You know,before she killed herself.
在她自杀之前
Where's Richard? Did you ditch him?
他人呢？理查呢？ 你们甩了他吗？
After we stole his lunch money and gave him a wedgie.
对，在抢了他的午餐钱 还有拉了他内裤之后
What's the matter? He's parking the car.
你这人怎么搞的？他在停车
-Did you guys have fun? -Your boyfriend is so cool.
那你们玩得开心吗？ 你的男朋友真的好酷
He let us drive his Jaguar. Joey for 12 blocks. Me for 15.
对，他让我们开他的车 乔伊12条街，我15条街
He must like you best.
他一定最喜欢你
What about when he tipped the guy who showed us to our seats?
还有他给那个 帮我们带位的人小费那件事
You never even saw the money.
他连多少都没看，就像这样
Hey,Chandler,thanks for showing us to our seats.
钱德，谢谢你帮我们带位 不用客气
You're welcome. Hey,Joey, thanks for parking the car.
乔伊，谢谢你帮我停车
No problem.
没问题
-Hey,Chandler -I think they get it.
钱德… 我想她们懂了
There's the man!
他来了
Hey,you're getting better.
你越来越行了
I'm gonna keep this.
对了，我要留着这个
He kept my dollar.
他留下我的钱
Your first weekend without Ben. What are you doing?
第一个没有班的周末 你们两个要做什么？
We're going to colonial Williamsburg.
我们要南下去威廉斯堡玩
A woman I went to college with is the first female blacksmith there.
对，我大学一个女同学 刚成为那里第一个女铁匠
They're a little behind the times in colonial Williamsburg.
威廉斯堡那边是有点落伍了
Look,I better go before Mommy starts weeping.
好吧 我们最好在掉眼泪之前走了
-We love you. -Bye,Mommy.
我们爱你 再见，妈咪
Have a good time.
好好玩
Look.
看
Joey,do you know we can see you from here?
乔伊 你知道我们看得到你吗？
How come Richard looks cooler with one of these?
为什么理查抽起这个 比我酷那么多？
You may wanna light it and lose the spatula.
首先，你或许要先点燃 还有放下那支锅铲
It's cute,you trying to be more like Richard.
你想模仿理查，我觉得很可爱
Not like him,per se.
也不是这样
Just not unlike him.
只是不要不像他
It's the artist formerly known as Chandler.
看，是以前 叫钱德的那个艺术家
I'm just trying something here, you know?
我不过是想试试看
Why didn't you grow a mustache?
乔伊，你为什么不留胡子？
We flipped for it.
我们丢铜板
I got the cigar, he got the mustache.
我丢到抽雪茄，他丢到留胡子
If we both grew them, we'd look like dorks.
我想我们都留的话会有点驴啦
You really sidestepped that land mine.
是呀，你们真的躲过那一劫了
I promised Richard we'd meet him downstairs.
我们得走了 我答应理查在楼下见
You're meeting Richard?
你们要见理查？
-Ranger game. -Didn't he tell you?
对，我们要去看曲棍球赛 对，他没告诉你吗？
He said he was going out with the guys. I didn't know that was you.
他告诉我他跟男人出去 我只是不知道男人是你们
You hear that?
你听到了吗？
We're the guys!
我们是男人
With that mustache, he reminds me of Aunt Sylvia.
钱德留那胡子 像不像西维亚姑妈？
Thank you!
谢谢
中央公园
Hi. We're visiting.
我们来拜访
It's Ben and his dada.
是小班跟他爹爹
Can you say "dada"?
爹爹，你会说“爹爹”吗？
I'm telling your mommies you said it, so you might as well.
你妈咪们说你说了，你试试啊
No luck,huh?
运气不好？
A while ago, I got a "seh" out of him...
不好，不久以前 他发了一个“二”的音
...which I thought might turn into "seh-condary caregiver," but....
我想那也可以勉强说 是二褓姆的意思…
Would you hold him for a sec? I gotta take this off.
帮我抱一下，好吗？ 我得把这个拿下来
Sure. Okay.
好的
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
I'm holding Ben.
我在抱班啊
He's a baby,not a bomb.
对，他是个婴儿，不是炸弹
Hold him like you'd hold a football.
你可以像抱足球那样抱他
This is how I would hold a football.
我就是这样抱足球的
Here. Here. There we go.
来…好了
Sorry,I'm not very good with babies. I haven't been around them.
对不起，我不太会带孩子 我是说，我没接触过他们
I mean,you know,since I was one.
从我长大以后啦
-It's all right. No big deal. -Really?
没关系，没什么大不了的 真的？
I'm sure you'll feel different when it's our baby.
我相信如果他是我们的宝宝 会让你完全改观
-What? -What?
什么？ 什么？
You think about stuff like that?
你想那一类的事？
Yeah. I mean....
对，我是说…
Actually,I kind of think that we'll have two babies.
事实上，我想我们会有 有两个宝宝
Two babies?
两个宝宝？
You know,a boy and a girl.
对，一男一女
Hopefully,the girl will come first, so Ben won't feel competitive.
我希望先生女的，所以小班 不会觉得有太大的竞争
Then what's gonna happen?
那接下来呢？
We won't wanna raise kids in the city, so we'll move to Scarsdale.
我们不希望孩子在城市里长大 所以我们或许会搬到史卡戴
We'll be far enough from our parents so we don't have to see them...
我们会住得离我们的父母够远 所以不用常常看到他们…
... but close enough that they can baby-sit.
…但又不会太远 所以随时可以请他们来带小孩
And yes,I know the taxes are a little higher than Nassau County...
没错，我知道那里的税 是比那梭郡要高一点…
... but the school system's great.
…但学校制度据说非常非常棒
Wow,that's great! Great!
太棒了…
Okay,wow! You know what?
你知道吗？
I'm off my break now.
我休息完了
Here. You take this.
所以你拿着
I'm gonna go pour these very nice people some coffee.
我要去帮这些好人倒咖啡了
Look at that. I don't have a pot.
你瞧瞧，我没有咖啡壶
I don't have a pot. Maybe I've got one at home.
或许我家里有一个
Or in Scarsdale. Hey,is that a door?
或是史卡戴，那是门吗？
Hey,Pheebs. What's happening?
菲菲，怎么了？
Murder,cancer,soccer teams eating each other in the Andes.
谋杀，癌症 足球队在安地斯山脉吃来吃去
So you watched the movies?
你看了电影了？
What is happening to the world?
这个世界到底怎么了？
I mean.... No,no,because E.T. Ieaves...
我是说，因为ET走了…
...and Rocky loses. Charlotte dies.
…洛基输了，夏绿蒂死了
Charlotte who?
哪个夏绿蒂？
With the web. The spider.
跟蛛网，那只蜘蛛
She dies. She has babies and dies.
它死了，它生了宝宝后就死了
It's like,"Welcome home from the hospital." Thud!
那就像…“欢迎从医院回来”
You wanna feel better?
想不想舒服一点？
Here. Watch this.
来，看这个
It's a Wonderful Life. I've heard of this.
“人生真美妙”这个我听说过
So you can't lose. It's there in the title.
所以没问题，片名说明了一切
Wonderfulness is baked right in.
包你美妙得不得了
I fell for that with Pride of the Yankees.
拜托，我差点就被 “北方佬的骄傲”给骗了
I thought I'd see a film about Yankee pride.
我以为我要看的是 关于“北方佬的骄傲”
And boom! The guy gets Lou Gehrig's disease.
然后… 那个砘锏昧寺犯鹑鹬
The guy was Lou Gehrig. Didn't you kind of see it coming?
那个砘锝新犯鹑 你没预感吗？
Watch that. It'll restore all your faith in humanity.
你看就是了，我保证能 让你恢复对人类的信心
Hey,big guy. Game time.
大个儿，球赛时间到了
-Hey! Be right there! -There's a game?
好，马上来 有球赛
I just got my Pik-Up Stiks back from the shop.
对，我刚从店里 拿了棍子玩具回来
Bring your nerves of steel.
带着你的铁胆来
It's the basketball playoffs.
是篮球决赛
I appreciate this,but you don't have to hang out with them for me.
亲爱的，我不喜欢你这样 但是你不用为了我跟他们混
They have each other.
反正他们两个可以做伴
Oh,no,honey. I mean,don't worry.
不，亲爱的，别担心
I like hanging out with them. They're different than my other friends.
我很喜欢跟他们混，很好玩 他们跟我别的朋友不同
They don't start sentences with "You know who just died shoveling snow?"
他们不会一见面就说 “你知道谁铲雪时死了吗？”
All right,that's great. Then just go.
好吧，那就去吧
Go Nicks!
加油，尼克队
It's the college playoffs.
是大学篮球决赛
-Then,go Vassar! -They're not in it.
加油，瓦萨 他们没比
Okay,then just go.
那加油吧
Why does this bother me so much?
我为什么要那么在意呢？
I'm not one of those people who wants to spend 24 hours a day together.
我并不想当那种要男友 24小时都跟她们在一起的人
Sure.
对呀
He just doesn't have much free time. What do I do?
只是他空闲的时间不多 我不知道，我到底该怎么办？
Does it matter? You'll just die or divorce or blow your pet's head off.
有关系吗？你始终都会死 或离婚，或枪杀你的宠物
Me too!
我也是
Rachel,I got a question. Richard made plans again with the guys
瑞秋，我有个问题 理查又跟他们做计划了…
Ross made plans for the century.
对，罗斯刚计划了整个世纪
I'm gonna go read Cosmo. Maybe there's something helpful in it.
我想我要回房去看杂志了 或许会读到什么有用的
If not,I can learn how to do a bikini wax with leftover Christmas candles.
不然至少可以学会 怎样用圣诞树剩下的蜡烛除毛
What happened back there?
你刚刚是怎么回事？
I don't know. You tell me.
不知道，你告诉我吧
One minute I'm holding Ben, then I've got two kids...
我刚刚还像抱足球一样抱着班 接下来我就有两个孩子…
... I'm living in Scarsdale complaining about taxes!
…住在史卡戴，抱怨着税太高
Well,I'm sorry. I think about stuff.
那抱歉，我就是爱东想西想
You're at work,you're assembling bones, your mind wanders.
我是说，工作的时候 一边弄骨头就会一边乱想嘛
You've planned out the next 20 years. We've dated for six weeks!
你计划了我们往后二十年生活 我们才在一起六周
You never think about our future?
你从不想未来的事吗？
I think about whose apartment we'll sleep at tomorrow...
想，但我想的是 我们明晚住谁那边好…
...and where we'll have dinner next Saturday!
…下个礼拜六晚上 我们去哪里吃晚饭
I do not think about our children's names!
我不会去想 我们的孩子会叫什么名字
You know what our children's names will be?
你知道我们的孩子 会叫什么名字？
No,I mean,you know. I read a book, and there was a girl named Emily.
不…我…我是说我看到一本书 里头有个女孩叫蜜莉
And I thought that might be good.
我觉得…我觉得还不错
What book?
哪一本书？
The Big Book of Children's Names.
“儿童命名大观”
Okay,listen.
你听着
What we have is amazing.
我们在一起很棒
But I do not want everything decided for me!
但我不要别人为我决定好一切
I spent my whole life like that.
我那样过一辈子了
It's what I had with Barry. That's a reason I left.
我跟贝利就是那样 那是我离开的原因之一
I like not knowing right now.
我喜欢有未知
Sorry if that scares you,but if you wanna be with me,deal with that!
如果那样吓着了你，那很抱歉 但若你要跟我在一起就接受吧
-Okay,fine! -Thank you!
好，很好 谢谢
-We're not done! -I didn't know that.
还没完呢 那我不知道
You're with a guy who won't stop planning his future with you.
跟你在一起的人 不会停止去计划他跟你的未来
He knows we'll end up together.
因为他知道我们最后会在一起
If that scares you,tough! You'll have to deal with that.
如果你害怕了，很不幸 因为你必须学会接受
-I will! -Good,because I love you!
很好，我会的 好，因为我爱你
Oh,yeah? I love you too!
是吗？我也爱你
-That's the first time we've said that! -Yes,it is!
我们第一次互相说我爱你 没错
-I'm gonna kiss you! -You better!
那我就要亲你了 最好是这样
Thanks for the great movie tip.
谢谢你给我的建议
-Did you like it? -Oh,yeah.
你喜欢吗？ 喜欢
I don't know if I was happier when George Bailey destroyed the business...
我不知道我是该在 贝乔治毁了家庭事业之后…
...or Donna Reed cried or when the pharmacist made his ear bleed.
…还是在李唐娜哭是在药剂师 害他耳朵流血时会比较快乐
I'll give you the ear thing, but wasn't the ending wonderful?
好吧，我选耳朵流血 你不觉得结局满好的吗？
I didn't watch it. I was too depressed.
结局我根本就没看 我太沮丧了
It kept getting worse! It should've been called:
剧情越来越叫人家失望 这片子应该叫：
"It's a Sucky Life,And Just When You Think It Can't Suck Anymore,It Does!"
“人生真衰就在你觉得 无法更衰时，它更衰”
IKick,save! And...
我踢球…
...denied!
…接住
He gets it back. Pass to the middle,lines it up....
但他抢回来，传到中间 然后准备踢，碰…
Yes!
太棒了！
Could that shot be any prettier?
那球还可以踢得更漂亮吗？
Man,you are incredible.
老兄，你真厉害
We had a table in college.
我们大学时也有这玩意儿
Really? I didn't know they had foosball in the 1800s.
我不晓得 1800年也有桌上足球
Nice mustache. At puberty, that thing will really kick in.
对了，你的胡子不错 青春期一到就会茂盛起来
Not to sound too Florence Henderson, but dinner's on the table.
我也不想太像个好太太 但晚餐做好了
One more point.
再玩一下
Score!
得分
Now can we go?
可以走了吗？
That's why we don't let her play.
看吧，所以我们才不让她玩
Is everything all right?
一切都还好吧？
Don't be mad at him. It's our fault.
听我说，别跟他生气 是我们的错
I'm sorry we've been hogging his time.
我们占了他太多时间了
He's just really great to hang out with.
是呀，跟他真的是很棒
-Well.... -No,seriously.
这个嘛… 不…说真的
We just talked about this. He is so much cooler than our dads.
我跟钱德刚才还在说 他比我们的爸爸酷多了
Our dads are okay and all, but Richard is just
我是说我们爸爸是还好啦 可是理查好…
What are you kicking me for?
你踢我干什么？
I'm trying to talk here.
我正在讲话，你…
You guys see me as a dad?
你们觉得我是父字辈的？
-Oh,yeah! -No!
对呀 不
You're just clearly not familiar with our young persons' vernacular.
你很显然不了解 我们年轻人的用语
When we say "dad," we mean "buddy."
我们“爸爸”的意思是指兄弟
We mean "pal."
是“伙伴”的意思
No,seriously. Joey's my dad.
我说真的，乔伊他是我爸
Monica's my dad.
摩妮卡也是我爸
I've even got some dads down at work.
我们公司里还有一些我爸爸
That's fine.
没问题
Well,your other dad and I are gonna go have a romantic evening.
你们的另外一个爸爸跟我 要去有一个浪漫的夜晚了
I'll just see you kids around.
孩子们，我们改天见了
Nighty-night.
晚安了
You're not a dad!
你不是一个爸
I can't believe you got us into trouble.
真不敢相信你干的好事
So are you okay?
你还好吗？
Just...
很好…
... I feel like I'm about a hundred.
…我只是觉得自己好老
I thought I was just one of the guys.
我还以为我跟他们一样
Come here.
过来
I'll make you feel like one of the guys.
我会让你觉得 你跟他们一样
For a really cool guy, you suck at foosball.
对一个很酷的人来说 你的足球烂透了
I was killing them.
我痛宰了他们
Yeah,well they suck too.
他们也很烂
You take the poopy diaper and put it in the poopy diaper pail.
对，然后你把有便便的尿布 丢到便便尿布桶里去
Calling it a "poopy diaper" doesn't make this process any cuter.
美其名为便便尿布 并不会让这个过程更可爱
-It's us. -Come on up.
是我们 上来吧
I'll get his stuff together.
我去准备他其他的东西
Okay,we can do this now, can't we,Ben?
我们做得到的，是不是，班？
Yes,we can.
对，我们可以
There! I did it!
好了
I did it!
我换好了
Look at that!
你瞧瞧
It stays on and everything.
紧紧的包在屁屁上
I'm sorry. What did you just say? Did you just say "hi"?
对不起，你刚刚说什么？ 你刚刚说“嗨”啊？
Oh,my God! Ross? Ben just said hi!
天啊，罗斯… 班刚说“嗨”耶
-What? -Ben just said hi!
什么？ 班刚说“嗨”
What,the word "hi"?
什么？嗨那个字？
No,my Uncle Hi.
不，我的嗨舅舅
Great! And I missed that too. I miss everything!
棒透了，我也错过了 我错过一切了
Oh,I'm sorry. I guess I just bring it out in him.
我猜我太有魅力了
-Where is he? -We missed you.
他在哪里？ 我们想你
We missed you so much! Come here,Ben.
我们好想你 过来，班
Guess what? Ben just said his first word.
你们猜，班刚说了哪个字？
What did he say?
他说什么了？
Something about hi.
什么嗨不嗨的
That's so exciting! Mommy's so proud of you!
真是令人兴奋 妈咪好骄傲哦
You know,actually, it's more like,hi!
事实上比较像这样，“嗨”
This could go on for a while.
这可能要玩很久
You're right. We've got a cab waiting.
计程车还在楼下等我们呢
Well,this was fun.
这真好玩 好的
We should do it again sometime,Ben. What do you say?
我们改天一定还要这样子 班，你说怎么样呢？
-All right,so I've got him...? -Tuesday.
好吧，下一次是… 礼拜二
Bye,you guys.
再见了
-Take care. -Bye,Ben.
保重 拜，班
Did he just say "bye"?
他刚刚…他…他刚刚说拜吗？
He said bye!
他说拜…
You said bye! He said bye to me!
你对我说拜，他对我说拜
Yes,he did!
没错
Suddenly I'm seeing him go off to college!
我已经可以幻想他去上大学了
We've gotta go. We've got that cab downstairs.
我们得走了，计程车在楼下等
See you later.
拜拜…
Look at this nice deep hole I dug. Hey,Bert...
我看挖的这个洞好深 柏特…
...isn't this a nice hole here?
…这洞是不是挖得很好？
Ben,this is the part where Ernie buries Bert in the sand and can't find him.
班，这是在演厄尼把柏特 埋在沙里头，然后找不到他
Now,I've looked ahead on the tape, and he does find him again.
现在，我已经先看过了 他后来有找到他
But before that happens, there's some rough going for a while.
可是，在那之前呢 会先有一些让人很难受的
But I think we can handle it.
可是我想我们挺得住
And there's just the alphabet, but we know that ends well,so....
这些只是…只是字母而已 可是我知道结局会很好的…
Here we go.
好，继续了
Bert? Bert?
柏特？… 他刚刚还在这里
What happened to my friend Bert? He was here just a moment ago.
我的朋友柏特怎么了？
Oh,no! My old friend Bert is lost.
不，柏特不见了？
I'm so glad you're here.
我真高兴你在这里
Bye-bye,baby.
拜拜，宝贝